highposition.net 2011-03-13

# Privacy Policy

"We" are High Position Limited, we provide this website as a public resource for information regarding our company and our products and also as a valued added service for our registered clients to access their personal information and other services we may offer through the member login facility.

## Introduction

We are committed to protecting your privacy. This policy explains how and for what purposes we use the information collected about you via [www.highposition.net](http://www.highposition.net/) (referred to below as "this Site"). Please read this privacy policy carefully. By using this Site and any services we offer via this Site, you are agreeing to be bound by this policy in respect of the information collected about you via this Site.  
If you have any queries or comments about the policy or our use of your personal information, please get in touch with us by emailing us at [privacy@highposition.net](mailto:privacy@highposition.net?subject=Privacy) or writing to The Privacy Manager at High Position Limited The Octagon 27 Middleborough Colchester CO1 1TG   
In general, we use the information we collect about you to:

  * help our members provide more personalised services to you 
  * provide information services to relevant third parties 
  * improve the features and services we offer 
  * support our own marketing and promotion efforts. 

### Personal information collected

When you visit, register or use the services on this Site, you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself, including your name and your contact details. We may also collect information about your use of this Site as well as information about you from the emails or letters sent to you. Finally, we may collect information about your property and the type of property you wish to purchase as well as the businesses you search for.

Your information will enable us to provide you with access to all parts of this Site and to supply the services and features that you have requested. We may aggregate the information to identify patterns which we can use in our marketing and to help us develop, administer, support and improve our services and features.  
In particular, we may use your information to contact you for your views on our services and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to this Site or our services. Further, where you have consented, we might also use your information to email you with details about any other products or services which we offer which may be of interest to you. If you change your mind about being contacted in the future, please email us at [privacy@highposition.net](mailto:privacy@highposition.net?subject=Privacy) and tell us.  
The following features, by their nature, require and make use of personally identifiable information.

## Registering with us

If you register with us, we save the details you provide and use them to enable us to personalise the service we offer to you. You can update 'your details' at any time via the sites member area.   
Registration with us will mean that you authorise us to occasionally send you promotions of our own and any business we deem suitable.

### Who has access to the information you provide or we collect?

We retain access to all personal information that we have collected from you.  
When our service is available via the websites of our partners, those partners may have access to your information. Their use of your personal information is governed by their privacy policies. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any other websites, even if you access them using links from this Site or if you can access this Site or use our services from them. We therefore recommend that you check the policy of each site that you visit and make sure that you are comfortable with the terms of such policies before providing any personal information.  
If you have consented on 'your details' page or the appropriate email form, we may provide any of the information we collect to carefully screened third parties to contact you regarding products or services that we think may be of interest to you. If you change your mind about being contacted by these third parties in the future, please email us at [privacy@highposition.net](mailto:privacy@highposition.net?subject=Privacy) and tell us.  
If our business enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners.  
We will not otherwise disclose, sell or distribute your information to any third party without your permission unless we are required to do so by law.

### Access to, changing or removing the information we hold

Registered users of this Site can update their information, change settings or cancel their membership on their 'members area' page once signed in.  
Non-registered and registered users of this Site can request we provide them with a copy of the personally identifiable information we hold via [privacy@highposition.net](mailto:privacy@highposition.net?subject=Privacy). You may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that such information is accurate and kept up-to-date. We may charge a small administration fee to cover the data search, preparation and delivery.

Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enable us to personalise your visits to this website, simplify the signing-in procedure, keep track of your preferences and to track the usage of this website. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored in the hard drive of your computer by your browser. Your browser will have the option to prevent websites using cookies (your browser's help screen or manual will tell you how to do this), but please note that this may reduce the functionality of this Site and other websites.  
Like all websites, our servers automatically record 'log files' containing information about the volume and characteristics of our website traffic e.g. IP address, numbers of pages viewed, length of time spent on site. We use log files to build pictures of how our site is used that help us to monitor and improve the service. We cannot identify you from your log files.

## Security, storage and transfer of information

We follow strict security procedures to ensure that your personal information is not damaged, destroyed, or disclosed to a third party without your permission and to prevent unauthorised access to it. The computers that store the information are kept in a secure facility with restricted physical access and we use secure firewalls and other measures to restrict electronic access.  
All of the information we collect or record is restricted to our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. We will explicitly ask you when we need information to identify you. We may require you to co-operate with our security checks before we disclose information to you. You can update the personal information that you give us at any time by viewing 'your details' page.  
Your information will not be transferred outside of the European Economic Area.  
We will retain your information for a reasonable period or for as long as is required by law.

### Changes to the policy

We may change this policy from time to time as we add new services or features or in response to changes in the law or our commercial arrangements. Any changes to this policy will be posted on this Site
